Meet the last man standing.
Blood and Bone is a action, crime, thriller film directed by Ben Ramsey.
In Los Angeles, an ex-con takes the underground fighting world by
storm in his quest to fulfill a promise to a dead friend.
Isaiah Bone, played by Michael Jai White.
James, played by Eamonn Walker.
Angela, played by Michelle Belegrin.
Tamara, played by Nona Gaye.
Pinball, played by Dante Basco.
Roberto, played by Dick Anthony Williams.
Blood and Bone is a 2009 American martial arts film directed
by Ben Ramsey and written by Michael Andrews.
It stars Michael Jai White, Julian Sands, Eamonn Walker, Dante
Basco, Nona Gaye, Michelle Belegrin, and Bob Sapp.
The film also features martial artist Matt Mullins, former professional wrestler
Ernest "The Cat" Miller, Kimbo Slice, Maurice Smith, and Gina Carano.
It was released direct-to-DVD on September 15, 2009.
The film explores themes of fight, tournament,
kick, prison fight, inspirational.
The tone is emotional and intense.